[Music]
Inside this class of algorithms, which I really thought I'd spent a lot more
time on, but they're really running out of
time, so I don't want to spend time
matching time on, so I get on to talk about other
topics in this information, so give something called a
contextual branch, okay, so
what are contextual bands, one way
you think
relaxing, I band it assumption date is
no state
from, I
immediate travel problem,
right, no, so what did the meet it, I bill
problem head, it head, which this explore it
up, right, date you cosy city date, d
noise in, d selection, right, it head, d
fact date I know about, d rewards
only through sampling, I don't know, d true
underlying reward distribution, so all of this
characteristic of, d reinforcement
learning problem, it had, right, so what is,
d third, I think they're doing, no, we're
adding this state dependent, right, in
different  Status I am going you have
different kinds of reward functions so what is till
missing sequential depends remember stocking
you award when
cycling you know it make an mistake initially
but give date is going you
influence be hard it is going you be
balance in de later stage right so I don't have
sequential bill depends no date I
so I give you an state you give me an action
right independence of what action you
selected bill give in other state
going like this so essentially what you are
going you do is look at an input and give you are
going you take an action
problem solving asset of band it
problems
right and I bill tell you come every point which
banded problem you are going you solve
okay here is problem three tell me what is this
option here is problem five tell me what is this
your option right de right so one
new way you think about solved  This is when it's not really nice if the way I have
stated the problem okay it's pretty nice
so one way of solving this is essentially share it okay I'm going to
maintain suppose I have
10 different branded self
maintain 10 different sets of action values
and 10 different sets of policy rights
going to do this which is independent and solve it okay so that's one way
of handling it but what I tell you
date these problems
can be mini note just like handful
but I'm going to have you have set of problems
per example I told you
one of the success story of
reinforcement planning was and
like this new story selections and all the
selection
examples where I said yahoo choose all the new
story you show on the web page treating it
as essential problems right so I have like
20 news story
when somebody comes to the web page I bill
Show us one out of d twenty story like
this is really like pulling and no and d day after tomorrow
clicks on it I get a reward
of one it and don't click on d story I get an
award of zero it is not a binary
binary problem but if all it is a
single bonded problem it is not very
interesting right because dat mens dat everybody am
com you d page Bill get shon d se news
story
and if you come back again and Bill get show on d se
new story it is that's not
going you be let not n good
think let what you really want you do is
defending on hukmus you your page right so you want
you be able to
change your choices
no you say dat I am going to group which d
people coming you me page right
from group three com used
you mini options here so you look at your
browsing history you look at fliff
already have an account on yahoo and
google and something you can look at it  Data is a
field of data and a variety of things are there
so you can look at which country they are coming
from what time of day they are clicking
from which they browsing from my phone and
from my laptop so match information data
one of the internet sites gather about you right no more about
you date you do right was
stupid today you think it is in fact people
and consciously not aware of their doing right but then
watching the person's behavior they are able to
form more an
informed model about you what you are
trying to do and what you are doing yourself what you are doing what you want
others so
fine so which kinds of things you can group
users its something you can do but it
look at which
variables it
of parameters
as
you want them you have some kind of grouping so
recently what this is also you do is it gives you
greater flexibility and
figure out what kind of  Generalization you want to happen over the
users right when I say
find group right and give assignment it
h group in some sense your making everybody
in d group have d se recommendation right d se
story it bill b sonate dem right doing this
kind of parameter is function
so you jump b sharing some parameter with us
on four accounts right so you should be
sharing parameter n three other
things right so essentially bill b like a
smoother generalization across people right so d
extreme how of this would b weer
everyone has a unique parameterization but if
you make everyone you 4th say you need d e
you are not doing match match generalization
right so essentially want some kind of
generalization so dat bill kid of who out from
doing this in n parameter express
d problem it one
of dem is you do this kind of
parameterization of the value defending on
the
d state
so I can think of it is new story one I can
also think of
Political
from India
right about the central
think of something of attributes that
describe the new story so well right so this
attribute to describe me am there not
describing me state so
in describing you so in this how
state and d people are coming to d page
and arms r d new story rights I could have
attribute describe both d new
story and the arms sorry and d users and I can use
which of these attributes to
define me l
function so I can have an
parameterization that depends on both d
actions like this
on defining me
value policies whatever it is people talk about
parameter spend it typically they talk about
parameter in d
value functions okay not necessary really in
kind of things and tha this is also form
of parameter and typically and people talk about
parameter is bonds in d contractual
bound how d talking  About parameters in
the
belly function okay
entertain me way in which
you can solve it you can just
replicate d band it you can do
gruv and year they don't really have to do something
so this again very very popular no in fact
most deployment of branded right him this
kind of
parameter contractually bonded so per
example give and of d most popular
deployment of UCB and I would b UCB is
wikham an
most popular band it algorithm right but
d most popular deployment of UCB
find it's called land you know which is UCB
with d linear parameterization as per d
elephant
and so forcibly what bring UCB
would do right and give they have to have some
mechanism by which determinants what
d immense confidence burns right so just likely
different update rule give what they do per
UCB but it's very are  Lee De Some
Principal
Something Like This So Three Tower One Tita You
Tita
So Next Class
[Music]
[Applause]